- One more question...
- Yes, you must be present to win.
(grunts)
(Zack:)Okay, I'm ready.
I'm Zach, and I'm, uh...
(Zack:)Oh, crap, why is this so hard?
(Penny:)Oh, hey.
(Leonard:)Hi.
Yo, P-dog.
(Penny:)What's up?
(Bernadette:)We're here to kidnap you
(Bernadette:)for a girls' night out.
Parenthetical: the term "kidnap"
is being used playfully.
(Penny:)I kind of figured that.
(Amy:)Good. Now put this pillowcase
over your head.
(Sheldon:)No.
(Amy:)She used to be much more fun,
(Amy:)until Leonard punched her
in the heart.
(Bernadette:)We just thought you
might want to go out
(Bernadette:)and have a good time,
maybe go dancing.
(Penny:)Oh. Gee, thanks, but I'm
not really in the mood.
(Amy:)You do understand
that it will distract you
(Amy:)from obsessing
over the rich variety
(Amy:)of sweet loving
that your ex-boyfriend
(Amy:)is currently receiving
from the fiery jewel of Mumbai.
(Penny:)Okay, look,
(Penny:)if I agree to go out
with you guys,